Welcome back.
I just made myself some nice hot coffee, and I'm ready to keep exploring here.
Now, I'm not sure what's going on with the little inscription we found inside the hat, but I did mark it as something I found inside the hat.
Oh!
Assume terminal!
Lovely view.
We get to see the desert in the back there.
Also, are those rivers down there?
I can't quite tell.
Let's engage the terminal.
Can we solve it immediately?
Okay, okay.
Tie fighter?
Ooh!
The warriors are speaking to the bards, and she doesn't seem impressed.
Maybe he's saying sorry or something.
Warriors love music.
We can say that for sure.
Warriors...
Now, let's see if I remember the actual symbol for this.
That one.
Yeah.
Warriors...
Ah, but hold on a minute here.
We have to remember the order is different for the bards.
Warriors love music, so it would really be music warriors love.
So go back.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Whoa!
We're all the way at the top!
Is this the last level?
I guess I'll find out.
Okay, let's see here.
So that would be...
Music warriors love.
So music...
I don't remember the symbol for that.
I think it is... Let me see.
That one?
No, okay.
I don't remember.
I have to go through all of them.
Oh, there it is.
Nice.
Music...
Warriors...
But plural...
So this guy and their...
Love.
Love-like.
Yeah, sweet!
Chosen one, come to the fortress!
And she's like, nope.
Okay, that would be... How would I write this?
Would I start with fortress?
To the fortress...
Come, chosen one.
Is that how Yoda would say it?
There's only three?
What?
There's only three glyphs here.
Fortress...
Go...
Chosen one.
I guess?
Let's see here.
That would be... Let's see if I remember this one.
Fortress...
Chosen one, go.
Right?
Or bard, in this case.
Bard, go.
Go pass.
Nailed it, man!
Nailed it!
Okay, what is she saying now?
Instruments, bards, possess.
Ooh, why is there so many glyphs here for that?
Ah, because of all the plurals.
Look.
So, instruments, bards, possess.
Bards, possess instruments.
So, we gotta start with bards.
I love how the language of these cultures kinda reflect...
The actual symbols, too.
You know, these ones are all rigid and very sharp angles and all that, like swords and warriors, right?
It's really neat.
Anyway, so, okay.
Bards, possess instruments.
So, we gotta start with bards or chosen ones.
I do not remember which one is chosen one here.
I have to go through... Oh, chosen?
But is that the same as chosen one?
I don't remember.
Chosen one?
It must be.
Ah, but wait, we needed plural first.
Shit, how do I revert?
Okay, so, plural...
chosen...
So, chosen, possess instruments.
Possess instruments.
Do they have a word for have?
Do we need that even?
Chosen ones...
possess instruments.
I think we do need that word for have.
Seek, want...
Ah, let's see here.
Instrument, okay, let's remember that.
Carry, possess...
Oh, yeah!
Nice, perfect.
Good, and now we need plural...
instrument.
Yes!
Music, bards love to play.
Bards love to play music.
Chosen...
Ah, shit.
Back again, we need to pluralize that.
Plural, chosen...
chosen ones love to play music.
Love, play music.
Right?
Does that make sense?
Do we have a word for love?
I think we do, but where is it?
Love.
Yep.
Play.
Oh, that's music, good to know.
I thought it said play.
It says lay.
Oh, there may not be a word for play.
Protect, warrior...
Oh my god, wait, what?
Maybe create music...
is what he means here.
I could see that happening.
You create music with an instrument, right?
Create music?
Yeah, beautiful.
To the fortress, bards will come!
Oh my god, everyone's going to the fortress.
Are they gonna have a concert for them?
Bards will go to the fortress.
Pluralized.
Bards...
go...
to fortress.
Where's go?
Go pass...
fortress.
And I think I remember the sign for that one.
It was a...
was it... was it that one?
No, shit.
I don't remember them.
Oh, fortress.
There it is.
He's so happy about it!
Yes!
Something has changed in the tower.
Okay, you know what?
Let's go explore the damn tower, huh?
In fact, I want to go back to the beginning now that we know some of this language.
And presumably something has changed down here too.
Let's go here.
Teleport me!
This was the very first terminal we found, I think.
Yeah, go up here.
Oh yeah, look at that!
The bards...
are playing games with the devotees.
The door is open!
Oh my god, look at that.
Ha ha ha!
This guy is vibing.
This guy is not having any of it.
Not quite, he's moving his head a bit.
He's afraid to show his emotions, you know?
Inside he's really enjoying the music.
I look kind of funny though.
I don't know, my character looks silly.
I don't know how to explain it, it's just...
He looks very muscular.
Or she, I don't know.
It's just funny.
I can actually go this way, let's see.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, there's a path here too!
What's going on down here?
There's a door there, but can we go further up?
A dirt pile.
Oh crap, let me take the other path.
Let's go this way first.
Oh, wait a minute, we're back here.
I was here earlier.
Well, at least in a similar place.
I'm going to keep going right, like a labyrinth, you know?
Proven technique.
Hopefully we're going to explore everything like that.
Seems like a prime area to get lost in.
Pillows.
Yeah, this is where we saw the dude.
Why is he dead down there?
Maybe it's one of the devotees that perhaps try to get to the next level.
Somehow he slipped past the gate and the warriors found him and killed him.
Very sad.
But I wasn't accessing this place via that entrance last time, was I?
Because that was close to me.
I went through the abbey.
Or did I?
Wait a minute, how did I actually go through last time?
Yeah, I'm not sure.
But I mean, I've been...
Oh.
What's this?
What did I just do?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, let me see, let me see.
I see water dripping.
And it stops.
Oh, that's right.
I remember something like that.
It needs to be in that position.
Otherwise there was water at some point and I couldn't progress.
Okay, go back out here.
But where was the last path I entered?
Or the access point?
Wait, this is where I came from?
Oh my God, I'm frickin' lost!
Oh my God, I'm so lost in here.
I have no clue where I am.
Uh, this way.
Okay, that's just a dead end.
I'm actually happy about that.
And this is gonna lead us back out where we came from?
I'm so confused.
Oh, that's right, that's how we accessed.
That's right.
Aw, little cat.
Okay, but...
And I guess the... Oh, oh, I remember now.
It just came back to me, I remember now.
So we went up here, of course.
We bypassed the warriors here and went straight up.
I don't know why I expected to find a completely new area, that's not how this is gonna work.
So yeah, that was a bit weird.
Let's see what else has changed here.
I really like this, it's nice.
They're all sort of... vibing together, it's so nice.
Surely there's nothing new down here.
This guy just sitting there still.
That guy has not been moving for a while.
Okay, well, we know the bards have now come to the fortress.
So perhaps I'll check that out.
But... let's quickly check this terminal down here again and see if we can't solve a translation problem.
Now that we know a bit of the language.
I mean, I guess we don't have everything yet, so this could be a challenge.
You help me.
You know what, I think I'm gonna wait with this until I have everything in this language.
Yeah, I'll wait with that.
But I will teleport.
Take me to... let's see here.
I want to go to the fortress now.
Let's go... here.
Two things, I also want to check if I can solve the puzzle here now.
But I think this was also...
Oh no, I can do this one, I can do this one.
I think... no, I don't have all the translations.
I'll be back, I'll be back.
But I gotta see what's changed.
Maybe I took a wrong or a very inefficient path here, but it's fine.
I actually don't remember the layout of this place.
I want to see the concert.
Yeah.
Oh my god, they actually consider the devotees impure.
That's crazy to me.
Chosen ones, the call.
They were called here.
Called by the tower.
Everyone's gone here, look.
Where have they gone to?
Maybe up here?
Even the guards up here are gone.
But I guess I did ring the bell and everyone sort of started running.
Bottles...
Also, notice something here.
The warriors await the call of the chosen ones.
I just made that call happen.
Right?
I connected them via the zoom terminal.
So that part is done.
The impure ones await death, that's grim.
Chosen ones that way.
Let's try going that way then.
No, no, no.
Ah, fine, let's try that way.
What could have changed in here?
And where?
Oh!
Yes!
I called it!
Look at that!
Honestly, I just guessed for fun that we're making a concert out of this.
That's amazing.
Hopefully they're not going to keep them here forever, you know?
And these guys are like bleeding from their fingers from playing and then when they're like, We're tired, we can't go anymore, they're like, Keep playing!
We need to hear it!
Until they eventually die and their fingers fall off and it's all a terrible tragedy.
I hope not!
I'm just imagining that.
That's great!
I like that!
Very nice!
Ah, this music is so nice.
I want to stay here a bit just to listen to it.
Go up here again.
I don't think anything's changed up here, but...
Maybe the dude is back up here sitting there with his bottle.
I wonder where the bellman went.
Probably joined the others for the concert.
I think it's so nice, it's a cool message in this game, you know?
Bringing cultures together like this.
Well, Tower of Babel, right?
Very, very amazing concept here.
Oh, I thought I could talk to them.
They're like, wow, look at that statue, that's a huge one, huh?
Got a sword as well, I wonder how they did that.
Wow, yeah.
Okay.
I guess it's time to go back up to...
Well, I don't have a zoom terminal right here, so I'm just going to do this.
I'm going to go back up to the alchemists.
And figure out the rest of that language.
Don't think there's any other zoom terminals I can complete right now.
I'm going to need to do the alchemist language first.
Wait, what?
Pass, barge, scan.
Pass, warrior... They put an X on it.
Oh, that's nice!
They're like, fuck that shit.
No more hating on the warriors.
Oh, that is nice.
Now I want to see what else has changed here.
Take me by boat.
Spin the rotors.
Fire up the engine.
I want to go over here.
What's over there?
Probably can't.
Maybe they say something else now.
Hey!
Speak to me.
Hello, a warrior, or are you?
You're not.
Weapons warriors have.
Idiots warriors are.
Oh, I thought you would have changed your stance.
They're not idiots.
They're just, you know, uninformed.
Same as you guys.
Everyone here is uninformed and, you know, language barriers and all that.
Yeah, I don't remember where the zoom terminals are here.
This is kind of a problem.
I think it was down in the Agora.
Look at me remembering the fancy names.
Down here somewhere.
What's happening here?
Yeah, no more wine for you.
No more wine for you.
In fact, something I noticed, was it only the...
Well, I don't want to call them slaves.
Maybe the helpers that went to the other place.
Because all these guys are just still being assholes.
I'm not entirely sure.
Like, these guys are just, where's my wine at, right?
And the two bards in the beginning are still calling warriors idiots.
Not sure how much are like that.
Well, the wine is flowing here.
They could just walk down here, you know, use their two legs.
And grab some wine for themselves, those lazy fuckers.
Here we go.
Give me that terminal.
Let's zoom it up.
No connection here.
I wonder if I can establish a connection here somehow.
And let's not forget, there's still these mysterious doors we need to explore.
But I think they're connected to, maybe solving all of these.
That would make sense to me.
Okay, let's go back up.
Transport me.
Nice.
So I haven't been down here yet.
A nice little shortcut.
Now, down here is where we found the door, I'm pretty sure.
Yep, there it is.
Still can't do anything with that.
Put the fork and knife in there.
No, I can't pick the lock.
Damn it.
Fine.
Guess I'll have to find the Tetris piece or whatever.
So I'm not sure where to go now.
Let's see the book.
Whoops, no, here.
Oh yeah, we had this thing.
Found in hat, that's right.
And this one is circled.
So we have gold, we have silver, we have copper and carbon.
Four elements.
Fairies.
Alchemist, bards, or brothers.
Why is that?
Why do they consider themselves brothers?
Do they just really like each other, or are they actually brothers in a weird way?
Maybe not literally, but...
Okay, fuck it, let's go this way.
Right.
Let's see the map.
Cafeteria.
We still haven't that one confirmed yet.
And there's something up here we haven't explored.
North of the cafeteria.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Plural found in hat.
So whatever this area is, has something to do with the hat.
Or at least what's written in the hat.
Something gold, something silver.
Not sure what that is.
Fairygate?
Oh, that makes sense.
So the mysterious doors are called fairygates, at least in the language of the alchemists.
Doesn't this, by the way, look like an oil rig?
This symbol here looks like an oil rig.
A little bit.
So where do I want to go first?
There's also this place down here, let's not forget.
Something copper, so these all three mean the same thing, and then copper.
Could be a copper refinery, or I don't know, smelter, you know, lab, who knows.
Something like that.
I want to see if I can find this place, so that means I got to go east from here and north.
And it was north of the cafeteria.
We know what you're saying.
This way?
Okay, so here's the cafeteria.
Ah, but it's not eating time, so I can't enter.
Not yet.
Are you guys saying something different now?
Cafeteria's closed.
It opens at...
uh, twelve.
Or at midnight.
Zero, zero.
Ah, probably midday, right?
It would be lunch.
So I guess we can...
uh, twelve?
Weird symbol for twelve, though.
Yeah, it's got to be twelve.
Are there any other numbers I haven't gotten yet?
Let's see.
Seven...
No, there's no other straight lines here, so that's how I know.
Yo, what if...
I don't know, something changes in the cafeteria at different times.
You know, they serve different foods, maybe a different door opens in there at different times.
What's down here?
Right, the stairs, okay.
Well, I guess I don't really have a choice.
I got to wait for the time here.
Also, did I just notice the time skip forward really fast when I went down here?
Nah, not really.
Does time pass when I open this?
Unfortunately not.
Okay, let me go look at the map in the meantime.
I do want to go into the cafeteria again.
Ah, wait a minute, maybe this doesn't mean north and south, maybe it means verticality.
What if I go up here again?
What was this way?
Oh, okay, right.
Right.
This weird machine.
Okay, so obviously silver, gold, copper and carbon.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, silver.
I know what to do.
I know everything.
Check this out, the way we're going to do this.
We are going to find different elements, okay?
We're going to turn them into ingots or bars.
And you know where we're going to do that?
Add the smelters or the refineries, whatever you want to call them on the map.
That's what they are.
We're going to smelt these things down into ingots.
And then they're going to fit into that machine.
Look at this, gold, silver, copper.
Ah, but wait, where's the last?
Maybe the last one, we're just going to find a carbon ingot?
Does that even make sense?
Would you make an ingot out of carbon?
I don't know about that one.
Let's head inside here again.
Let's see if anything's changed for lunch.
Give me food.
I want to eat.
Eating time.
I will never be late for the cafeteria.
I'll always be on time.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha.
I'm so well behaved, waiting for everyone else to enter first.
Are you saying anything else now?
Cafeteria open.
Yeah, we know that.
This guy's still sleeping.
Okay, it looks to be sort of the same.
Right, okay, okay.
I think... I'm not sure what this means though.
This could mean machine.
And what about this over here?
Oh!
Cafeteria door?
And... whatever that is.
Smelt?
Combined?
Is that what's going to happen?
We're going to put all these elements in and it's going to be combined?
In some way?
And we have a bunch of numbers here.
Yeah, this is... I'm not sure I understand this part yet.
But I kind of want to find areas where we get to fill out more in the book.
So perhaps we try to go down again to the first level.
And it keeps exploring because if we look at the map here, I want to try going here.
Especially now that we discovered the hat thing, right?
Something should be going on there.
Let's take the elevator.
Okay,
so have I even gone to the right in this place yet?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Talk to these guys.
I'm an alchemist.
Me greet you.
Thank you.
I am a nomad, I guess.
An unknown person.
Ooh!
Laboratory!
I don't think it's literal that this is a microscope.
It wouldn't be microscope, right?
It would be a lab or something.
Let's see here.
Fountain hat one, lab one, lab two.
And something that is broken, we can't see what that is.
In fact, I'm going to write lab on this.
Lab.
And then we have to remember that inside the lab, something like this is going to take place.
Whatever that is.
Numbers for sure.
Let's go in here.
Lab one.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh man, this area looks cool.
Let's see, let's see.
Kitchen, mines, lab, library.
Lab.
Cafeteria.
Mines?
Wait, do I have a word for that?
Oh god, I don't know.
Let's wait a bit.
Let's see here.
I see.
They need to combine different elements here.
In the machine, right?
Which will open the door.
To the next level, perhaps.
I mean, this almost looks like a zoom terminal, but it actually looks more like the big door we saw where the control panel was all fucked up.
As if someone had messed with it, right?
And left it in a big old mess.
Let's look at it.
Ah, we apply heat to the three elements.
In the machine.
And it will open the door.
Or power the door, perhaps.
Heat.
Let's talk to him.
We seek or want something.
We seek to operate the machine.
Elements?
We seek raw materials.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's just write elements.
Raw materials.
Raw mats.
I like that.
Okay.
What about you?
The fairies made the door.
The machine opens the door.
I'm going to call this the machine.
I'm pretty confident.
Machine.
Even though it should be a verb.
Apparently.
Why did I call it a verb?
Was it because...
Yeah, all these others are verbs, right?
Open, close.
What verb could also describe a machine?
Maybe ascent?
Is it ascent?
Because presumably opening the door leads to the top of the tower?
Now, I'm going to leave it on machine for now.
Even though I don't think it's correct.
Just because in my mind it makes the most sense.
For context purposes.
Also, you wouldn't say verb, open door, right?
Okay.
Who are the fairies though?
That's what I want to know at this point.
Let me see what other things are in here.
Can I click on stuff?
I want to take a closer look at all your lab stuff.
Oh, that's what I like to see.
What's going on over here?
Man, I'm really enjoying this level.
A measuring stick, look at that.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19.
Oh!
20, hold on a minute.
19.
Plus 5.
24.
Is that how I'm supposed to read this?
This one is 20.
Do I have a symbol for that?
Oh, I see.
Oh, interesting.
They turned them around.
Look, this is 1.
But now it's been flipped.
So this is now 10.
Oh, that's smart.
This is 20 because it's the flipped version of 2.
That's really cool.
So the side matters here.
So this would be 50.
And this would be 30.
80 in total.
80 plus 9.
89.
I'm not sure how that's going to help me with anything, but it's an interesting observation.
Notice also here at 11, it's 10 plus 1.
Right?
12 is 10 plus 2.
They combine them like that.
That's so smart.
So in that case, this would be 39.
Right?
39.
And then we have this up here.
Yeah, that is, I guess, 50.
Except I don't know what it means when it's up here instead.
So now I know what it means when they flip the numbers on each side here.
That's like adding 10 to it, right?
But flipping it up here...
The fact that it's on the left side means it's 50, but there could be another thing changing the idea here, right?
Because it's up here instead of down there.
Maybe it's just a space issue.
There's no more space for it.
I don't know.
But that is so cool.
What a really nice way to do numbers.
What's this?
Oh god.
Oh, it's a calculator.
1 plus 2 plus 7 plus 12.
Let's just do 1.
So what do we have?
We have 7 plus 2, that's 9, plus 1, that's 10, so that's 11.
And is this...
Actually, let's see.
Can we make it?
Oh my god!
Oh, okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Interesting stuff.
So, the first two are going to be what happens on the left here, perhaps?
Actually, no, no, no.
Can I reset this?
Just reset it completely.
There, there.
Keep it nice there, okay.
That's just a straight line.
So I guess I'm wrong with 12 here.
That is zero.
Okay, okay, okay.
So now if I go 1 here, this should just be 1.
Oh, what?
Oh, this is all the top part.
I see, I see.
Look, this is all the bottom part, so if I go here and do 1, it's going to be... No?
Okay.
What?
Okay, then I'm not sure I understand this.
Okay, what if I instead do here 1?
Aha!
All right.
And here?
That's 10.
Oh, 1, 100,000.
I get it.
Whoops.
This should be over here now.
Yep, and if I do this, this should be 11.
Yep, and if I do this, this should be 12.
No, no.
This should be 21, so that means 2 here, 1 there.
Yeah!
Sweet.
Okay, okay, interesting.
So, 1s, 10s, 100 over here, maybe?
Let's see.
I forgot.
So this should be 101.
Okay, yeah, I guess we don't need to have this one down here, then.
This would be 111.
Yeah!
Hey, hey, dude, that's sick.
What a great system.
I love this.
Very neat.
Oh, I guess the cafeteria opened again.
People are eating all the time here, eh?
Okay, let's see here.
So what about the bottom part?
What does that do?
Let's just reset it.
Let's do 1 here.
Okay, that's the same.
That's the same as well.
So what exactly is happening when I do... whoops.
Here and here.
Wait.
Oh, is it a... are they being added together?
That's 11.
Plus, let's say 2, should be 13.
So how would that look?
It would be 1 here with a triangle here.
Yes!
Okay, so it is adding together.
It is a calculator.
Let's see if we can predict some stuff here.
Let's say we go crazy.
Let's do this one, let's do that one, let's do this one and that one.
Let's see if we can figure this out.
So this would be 205 plus 3,020.
Right?
3,020 plus 105.
Oh god, that would be... hold on, I can't remember what I just said.
3,020, so that's 3,025 plus... 200, sorry.
So that would be 3,225.
So that would be a 3 here, a 2 here, a 2 here and a triangle there.
Yeah, no, oh yeah, 5 of course, because yeah, sorry, I meant to say circle here because 5.
Everything makes sense.
Love it.
That's incredible.
Oh yeah, 6.
Oh well, I don't know the 1 for 6 though.
I guess I haven't really... I guess I gotta go back to the watch.
No, actually I can just look at it here.
What am I doing?
So let's reset this.
I wish there was a reset button, just reset everything.
Actually, I guess I don't need to do this.
I can just sort of... 2, so... 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 is that one.
This is 6.
7 is that one, we know that.
8, okay, that's the little line through it.
8, 9, 10.
Well, yeah, yeah.
And then it goes back to the start, okay.
I guess that makes sense.
You wouldn't need more than that, right?
Just like our number system, you wouldn't have a...
Actually that makes a lot of sense.
It was kind of stupid for me to guess 12 on that.
Of course it's 0, right?
And I guess I have them all now?
Is there anyone I'm missing?
7, 6, 0, 8... I think I got them all.
Okay, so let's fill out the book.
6, 7, 8, and 0.
Oh, sorry, this one, this would be 9.
9, there we go.
Wonderful.
Nice.
Okay, very cool.
We got something on the drawing board up here.
Okay, let's see.
What are they trying to do?
They're trying to combine.
Let's try and read this.
Also, this is combinations.
Combination.
Yeah, I like that.
Okay, so here they're trying to do... Let's see if I remember, actually.
This one is copper.
I forgot what that one is.
Silver, okay.
Copper, silver, carbon.
Or gold.
Gold, silver... Oh, wait a minute, we have four elements, though.
What was this one again?
Carbon, okay, okay, good, good, good.
So gold, they needed how many?
They needed...
What is this?
19?
19 gold didn't work.
Oh, I see exactly what's happening here.
19 gold and...
Let's see if we remember this.
This is silver.
Is it silver?
I forgot already.
God damn it.
Yeah, silver, okay.
So this would be 1,241.
Was that the symbol for four?
Yep.
1,241.
And this one is copper.
So this would be 6,008.
Right?
Was that 8?
Yes.
So this combination didn't work.
They tried all these combinations, but we know of a combination, don't we?
Which is 5,039.
5,039.
Very cool.
It's the lone scientist up there, you know, in his study.
He figured out the solution.
But of course, first I'm going to need to get some elements here.
So I can go up this way or this way.
Let's try going up first.
Okay, so that leads us... I see, I see.
This way then.
Ooh, chemical spill.
What is that?
Monsters are afraid of fire.
Easy.
Monster, fear, fire.
Which makes sense.
They're afraid of light, right?
Oh yeah.
We're going to need to get a torch or something.
Butterflies and caterpillars?
Monster?
Afraid.
Elements?
That one?
I don't know about that.
What could that be?
Well, it's got to be this one, I think, or this one, whatever these are.
Because none of the other guesses I have here makes sense.
Could be life?
Nature?
Evolution?
Starts as a caterpillar, becomes a butterfly?
Or not evolution, more like growing up?
Or hatching?
Create?
Where's that?
There.
God's creations?
Okay, let's wait with that.
I also had this one, I didn't quite finish it.
This is the library, but don't we have a name for that already?
No, that was books.
And that one we got confirmed, didn't we?
Shit, I... I'm not sure.
Let's keep moving.
Actually, oh, look at that.
This is the word for minds.
Whatever that is.
So there's a line and a little circle.
A line and a little circle.
Could be that one.
Could be both of these, honestly.
But it's sort of close, it goes in.
It's this one.
This one is a triangle or top, you see that?
Do we have any other ones with a line and a circle?
No, we don't.
It's this one.
This is minds.
Or mine.
And the reason I'm saying that is because this is a sign pointing to where it just was, right?
Let's go in there again.
Just want to see what's in here.
Oh wait, I can't enter?
I guess I need light, right?
There's monsters in there.
Makes sense.
What is that over there?
Look at that guy standing there looking over things.
Lab two!
Oh yes.
Let's check it.
Oh, this... Okay, I see.
Well, shit.
What am I doing now, then?
I guess I'll maybe go to library, see if I can't find a word for library.
Are you saying anything else now?
I mean, maybe I recognize what you're saying now, I mean.
I think this means a send.
Because you don't seek a machine.
You seek to ascend, right?
You seek to go through the door.
You seek to combine?
Yeah, okay.
Back down.
And what was happening here?
Look at the way that things goes down there.
Yeah, this is that one.
It could also be that, I guess.
But the fact that there's a straight line up before, this is mine.
This, though, I don't know.
Is this consistent, by the way?
These are all locations?
Are there other location-looking glyphs here?
Doesn't look like it.
This could mean library.
Simply because it's the only one I have left, and it's definitely a place.
Could be a nice, educated guess.
Ah, we have this one.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Lab.
Right, it's a place.
Cafeteria, it makes sense, it's a place.
This, I think, means library.
I'm actually so sure I'm gonna put it in.
Okay, never mind.
Dang.
I was so sure of that.
But I guess it could also be another place.
I guess I felt like assuming it was the library, because, you know, it was the one the game was asking me for.
Labs.
Yeah, that makes so much sense.
So now we check that out.
Let's see the map again.
Oh!
I don't know what the English word is for this.
I think it's maybe called Refinery.
Is that what it's called when a place sort of, you know, smelts down metals or whatever?
I think so.
Refinery?
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Gold Refinery, Silver Refinery, right?
But this is broken, so how do we get down there?
We have to repair it.
Gold Refinery.
Oh yeah, there was something over here.
Put the forks in there.
Of course, that doesn't work.
Oh yeah, there's also this thing here.
That's gonna shoot that thing in there.
Okay, I'm not sure what's going on there.
This should lead us to Silver Refinery.
Let's go that way, actually.
Did I go down here?
Oh yeah, I need another access card.
How do I get those?
That's a mystery.
Okay, yeah, fine.
Just walk all the way up again.
Through the door.
I can't believe we haven't got a word for library, given where we are.
Let's see this again.
First, you open.
Then you put in Silver Golden Copper in the right amounts, I guess.
Then you check if this one is in the green, and if it is, you pull this lever, and then lastly, you press the button.
Yeah, but I don't have any of that right now.
I don't have any elements.
I need to re-smell these into ingots.
I am 99.99% sure that that's what's happening.
Create fire.
So we need to find this to get in the mines.
Do you know where fire is?
Are you searching for a book?
I am not.
I'm searching for fire.
Oh yeah, we know this is a gold ring.
Okay.
Is there really no word for library here, anywhere?
I need that word.
And what was this?
Oh yeah, brothers, that's right.
That's what we learned there.
Ah, this one, I think we solved that one completely.
Yeah, the fairies made the door.
I think the fairies are going to be the next area.
They're going to be fairies there.
But any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic, so what I imagine is going to happen is they're not actually going to be flying fairies, you know?
Doing magic.
They're just going to be a highly technologically advanced people up there.
Okay, so we've been here.
I'm not quite sure what to do at this point, I gotta be honest.
I'm a little bit lost.
I guess we can check the map again and see where we haven't been.
Let's see the map here.
So these two are off limits.
Can't go in any of these.
These are the labs.
This is the copper refinery, but we can't get down there.
And it doesn't seem to be...
Or it doesn't seem to be any way to get down there with stairs, right?
There's only an elevator.
And it's closed.
So maybe we can open this somehow.
Wait, the mine is there?
Wait a minute.
Something ate right here.
Maybe that's the library.
Wait, what?
Hold on a minute.
Go this way again.
Books.
Right.
This way was... Wait, what?
No, this leads to the library.
Maybe I'm wrong on that.
This is library.
Okay, I have no clue.
I don't know where to go.
I am super lost.
Where have I not been?
I've checked out the labs.
Going north from there goes to cafeteria?
I guess so.
Can I manually get down here somewhere?
Let's see if we can do that.
Is there a path down somehow?
South of here?
Where was the very first place I entered this area?
That was down in the mines, right?
I came from there.
Yeah, this is so confusing.
Yeah, this leads back up to the top floor of the library.
This makes no sense to me at all.
Maybe I got some of these wrong.
Wait a minute here.
I think I'm confusing myself so much.
Let's get rid of all of these.
I'm pretty sure this means mine because of what we deduced earlier with the whole, you know, line here and circle here.
This one, I don't know.
I'll remove it.
Cafeteria?
Why am I so sure of that?
Oh, because it was right above the cafeteria, right?
That one is sure.
Okay, wait a minute.
This is actually a... No, never mind that.
Yeah, never mind that.
Lab, that one we're sure of.
The only two we're not sure of are this one.
And there was one other, right?
No, it was this one.
That's why I guessed library, right?
Because it's the only one left.
But I guess we haven't found the last one because we still have some left.
What haven't I done?
Let's teleport to the other zoom terminal here.
Oh, there was just one.
Never mind.
Okay.
Oh, dude.
I don't remember where I even entered this entire area.
How did I get here?
It was from the mines, though, wasn't it?
There was a monster following me.
Wait, what?
I thought I was on the second floor.
Where am I now?
I am so lost.
Okay, so this is where I started.
This was the area I came to.
From down here, then?
Wait, where's that taking me?
A?
Oh, yeah, this is where we came from.
But this elevator isn't closed.
I'm losing my mind.
There is another zoom terminal.
I wasn't imagining things.
Wait, does that mean there's another zoom terminal here since there's a little line?
Bro, I am so confused.
Yeah, I must stop it here.
My brain is turning into mush.
Time to take a breather.
I'll see you in the next episode.
Thanks for watching.
Bye bye.